Cole Pergerson

San Jose, California, United States



linkedin.com/in/colepergerson



cole.pergerson@gmail.com

Summary

I'm learning about developing and designing games while studying at San Jose State University. I've worked on seven games while in university which can all be found on Itch.io. I enjoy talking about game design and helping others learn how to make games. Additionally, I have experience in team management from being the President of the fencing club and a producer for an indie game.

Experience



Game Programmer

Creaky Wrist House

Sep 2019 - May 2020 (9 months)

Worked on a 3D horror game with a team of 20 SJSU students for the Animation program.

Created a variety of gameplay features such as cutscenes and interactable hiding spots.

Worked with animators to solve issues and test animation files in Unity3D.



Fast Food Cook

Panda Restaurant Group

Oct 2018 - Apr 2020 (1 year 7 months)

Prioritized which entrées to cook during rush hours.

Handled multiple tasks in the kitchen at once.

Managed other cooks in the absence of leads.

Prepared vegetables and meat for cooking.

3D Environment Artist

Freelance

Oct 2019 - Nov 2019 (2 months)

Worked with a group of Digital Media Art students to create a Halloween themed art exhibition.

Held at the Hammer Theater during San Jose's monthly First Friday art event.

Used Blender to create a 3D render of an eerie environment.

Gained skills in storyboarding, composition, lighting, and creating materials.

Provided an entertaining experience for over a 100 people participating in First Friday.

■ Tournament Manager

Spartan Fencing Club

Mar 2019 - Apr 2019 (2 months)

Reached out to experienced fencers to hire as referees.

Managed the pooling and direct elimination of the tournament.

Quickly responded to injuries or other medical emergencies.

Hosted a competitive college tournament for over 90 fencers.

Office Assistant & Data entry

Pergerson & Assoicates

Aug 2015 - Jun 2017 (1 year 11 months)

Created 1000s of invoices for customers using Quickbooks Responded to customer emails about problems regarding their invoice.

Education



San Jose State University

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Digital Media Art

2017 - 2021

Creating art that asks critical questions using modern digital tools and technology. My focus is game design and web development.

I'm the President of the Spartan Fencing Club and my duties involve setting team goals, delegating tasks, reviewing progress, building a community, and advertising.

Skills

Production Management • Gameplay Programming • Cooking • Web Development • Unity • Full-Stack Development • Back-End Web Development • Quality Assurance